Thank you for watching!
Thank you.
Okay, bye.
Hello! Ste, this time we have with us Isereira from Angulum.
and Natsumizu Rocco from Ocha-no-Oma!
We're going to be talking about the two of us, so please bear with us until the end.
Both Angulum and Ochanooma are currently on their fall tours.
Do you have a theme for this fall tour?
Yes, for me it is to improve my singing skills.
How do you see it?
The acoustics change depending on the venue.
I don't want to be affected by it.
I want to be able to sing more without changing the stability of my singing.
And as for me... the theme for the fall tour of Ise is...
The group has changed and there are now 11 members.
And now that we have junior members, I have a better idea of where I stand.
I have more junior members now, so I have more position than before.
So
I'm going to fulfill my responsibility
I have to fulfill my responsibilities.
I'm doing my best this time.
The remaining performances for Angelem are in Osaka on the 19th
and the Nippon Budokan on Friday the 24th.
The Osaka concert is the last one for Angelem as a concert hall, so I want to do my best until the end.
I'd like to do my best until the end.
The Nippon Budokan performance will be a little different.
I'm sure the contents of the Nippon Budokan show will be a little different.
I'll do my best so that as many people as possible will be able to see the show.
The tea ceremony will be held in Fukuoka on Saturday the 25th and in Oita Prefecture on Sunday the 26th. Yes, and the Uma of Tea will be in Fukuoka on Saturday the 25th and in Oita Prefecture on Sunday the 26th.
We have just started the Uma event, but we will be able to visit many places.
We are able to visit many areas.
I would like to do my best to enjoy the atmosphere of each area.
I'm going to do my best while enjoying the atmosphere of each area.
And Angelem's new single "Red Line Life is Booty" will be released on December 13th.
Red Line Life is Booty!
Beautiful will be released soon!
Thank you very much.
Red Line is one of the coolest things about Angulum, and
But it's also a new kind of coolness.
The group has changed, and there's a bit of freshness and a bit of desperation.
It's a cool song with a bit of freshness and a bit of desperation.
And "Life is Beautiful" is the opposite of that.
Angelem has some bright songs, but
but it's quite rare to find a song that's all about the cute side.
I think you'll enjoy the gap between the two.
Two new members, Yukiho and Hana Goto, have joined us to make 11 members.
As I said before, we are very fresh and energetic.
I can really feel their energy.
I would like to do my best with them while being influenced by them.
In terms of singing, I think it's great that we have more singing parts.
I'm also very happy that I've been able to sing more "hamori" parts.
Thankfully, there are more and more situations where I can make use of my low voice.
I'd like to continue to work even harder in the future.
Please take a look at this video.
Please take a look.
Thank you for watching!
Here we go!
Ami! Ami!
Saori!
Yubi!
Luna!
This is the last one, no matter if you cry or laugh!
I'm so glad that we have 11 members!
Daichi!
I know you must be nervous, but have fun!
Let's do it!
Camelia!
Wow!
Yay!
Oh, man!
Let's do it.
Ready, go!
Let's do it!
Let's go!
Let's have fun!
Why the hell not?
Oh, my God!
I don't know how many times I've hugged Kino-chan in my life. It's the best.
Hey, Sunflower.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I love it.
Thank you for your hard work.
Are you okay?Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I was wrong.
I love you. I love you so much.
I'm going to crush it.
Did you have fun?
Yeah, I did.
I'm having fun.
Super fun.
Riko is that way?
There or there?
I'm off.
But I'll see you soon.
I'll see you there.
First things first.
Together.
Basically together.
We're going to look forward, right?
We're going to look forward.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 1 7, 18, 19, 20.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Let's go for a drink!
Bye!
Thank you for watching.
There's no darkness in the morning. Maybe that's what you hate.
But even on the hardest days, it's not all bad, is it?
Even when you're having a bad day, smile and be sadEven on days when you don't feel like it, smile and be sad.
I'm not as soft as I think I am
Even if the world changes its values
But what I love will never change
I want to make the best story I can.
I can't believe she's a sky witch. I'm the hero.
We've always been hobbies. We're both self-made men.
I can't be discouraged I've got to give it a chance
I'm gonna give it my all I'm gonna be brave I'm gonna be brave I'm gonna be brave I'm gonna be brave
I'm looking for you.
I'm looking for you. I'm alive with you.
You told me to take it easy, but I can't.
I don't have the dexterity to cut corners, so thank you.
I just want to be a little looser.
But what we accomplished that day...
I want to shine brighter.
I want to make the best story I can.
I'll take my chances as long as it's something Earth is comfortable with.
I'm trying to be the universe, and I'm trying, and everybody's last.
I'm not gonna stop, I'm not gonna give up, I'm gonna take a chance
Grab it, grab it, grab it, grab it, grab it, grab it, for the rest of your life
The light.
Through the rain clouds
Shining through the rain clouds
♪ Smiling faces that won't give up
I can laugh when I realize
I want to say it and do it and say it and say it and say it and say it and say it and say it and say it and say it and say it
Everyone who was born is useful to someone else
I want to make up the best story I want to make the best story I can.
Adam Anfang, even today.
I'm the hero of everything
I'm on my own home beat. I'm at the bottom of the pile, ready to go.
I can't run away from it, I can't escape it, I can't escape it, I can't escape it.
I can't run away from it, I can't escape it, I can't escape it, I can't escape it...
Adam Anfang Today, I'm still the hero
Ise Reira of Angulum and
and Rocco Doi from Ochanomama.
I'd like to talk a little bit about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer in a quick tempo.
Yes, I'll do my best.
It's been two whole years since I joined Hello Project.
What is the best word to describe these two years?
DOTO
My motto: "If you think you've had the most fun in the world, you've won.
What is the most enjoyable moment you've had in the world recently?
Right now.
What is the one thing that Rocco Doi wants to improve?
Girl power
What do you like about Leila Ise?
There are many things.
I like her face.
And her performance.
I like her sharpness in dance.
And her smoothness.
It's really something
Only Ise-san can do it. Only Mr. Ise can do it.
I really like your dancing.
It's so mocking...
And even though he's kind of mocking...
I love his sharp sense of humor.
I love it so much!
Thank you very much.
This year is the 25th anniversary of Hello Project.
Which song does Rocco Doi choose as the most attractive choreography?
Morning Musume。 s "Wakutekateka Chance"!
Oh!
I see.
There are a lot of things I'm interested in.
Which one should I ask first?
Well, let's start with the first one.
Let's start with...
It's been two whole years since you joined Hello Project.
I've been a member of Hello Project for two whole years next month.
Is there a word that best describes these two years?
Yes.
Raging waves.
I think there's a word for that.
I think that's a great word to describe what I've been doing.
I've been able to challenge myself in many different things every day.
I was able to challenge myself in many different ways every day, and I really formed a bond with the members.
I think I was able to spend every day with a lot of energy.
That's right, isn't it?
I guess...
When I was busy...
It's not like youth, but when we're all together, it's like we're busy. It's not like we're all young, but when we're all together, it's like we're busy.
It's not youth, but it's fun and it's great.
I understand.
And can I ask you something else that's really bugging me?
Um...
What is your favorite thing about Visela?
I thought I could ask you just one question.
But you said a lot.
Thank you very much.
I love it.
I'm very happy to hear that.
You've said so many things.
But there's more.
Oh, no.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I don't know what to do.
But you know, I like Manaka-chan.
No, no, no, no, no...
What's this?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
But... you always say so many things.
But it's not often we get to do something like this together.
I'm a really bad senior...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I made him say it.
I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
The question for Mr. Ise will come after the VTR. Yes, questions for Mr. Ise will be after the VTR.
Hallo! Halo!
Great, great, great, great!
That one lie can be the end of everything.
Morning Musume。23 す すごいフィーバー
Now on sale
Wake up call It's time to wake up
It's time to enjoy life
The sun is telling you that
Morning Musume。23 Wake up call
Wake up call Now on sale
If I may say so, what a stupid mama human being
Morning Musume。23 featuring Mizuki Fukumura
Never ending shine Now on sale
Koukou de Red Line Hurt, I want to hurt, I want to hurt
I do I do Ai no Saber
Anjumu Red Line December 13 on sale
Seino
Tsubaki Factory.
Tsubaki Factory Concert Tour 2023 Autumn Atara yo
Riko Yamagishi Yoshimoto Yume's Graduation Special AKATSUKI finished
It's over!
It's over, isn't it?
It all happened so fast.
Before it started
I don't know. I didn't have much time.
But a lot of the members were saying that.
But you two...
I saw them singing solos.
And expressing their feelings. I saw him tell her how he felt.
I'm starting to realize that I'm graduating.
I see.
That's how I feel.
The live show itself was different from what I thought the fall tour would be, and the set guests were different.
I think we were able to enjoy the show with a fresh feeling.
I think this is the first time I've ever felt like the title of the tour fits so well.
I wanted to open the door to a new world.
That's what it means.
I really wanted to stay like this forever.
You two were so beautiful.
They were so beautiful.
I thought, "I'm going to do my best.
I'll do my best.
After I sing this part.
I'll never get a chance to sing with you again.
I got really sad.
I felt the importance of singing each song and each part
I felt it more than ever.
I really, really felt it.
I remember somewhere during the concert tour, Mizuko said...
Mizuko said somewhere in the hall tour
I heard Mizuko said that she wanted the audience to speak out loud enough to break through the monitors in our ears.
Like at the Budokan.
I could really hear the audience.
I could really feel the enthusiasm of the audience.
I could feel the passion of the people who love Tsubaki Factory until the end.
I was so happy that I was able to be a part of it, just like Tsubaki.
I felt like this in the rehearsal.
I saw the surprise that wasn't in the rehearsal. I wasn't at rehearsal, but I saw the surprise.
Oh, yeah.
I love ricochet.
Oh, my God! What is that?
What is this? What is that?
What is that? Did you practice that?
I practiced the sound with my voice in it.
What's this? On the last day of rehearsal.
They said they were waiting for comments.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
That's the most nervous Ugo I've ever heard.
That's right.
Because you can't say it only at the venue
Right, right, right!
But you didn't tell us.
It's working.
I could feel it.
I'm so happy.
It was pretty close, seeing all those people crying.
It was close?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
I couldn't hold it in for a second because of the singing.
That was great.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
We're graduating today.
But there are so many things that I've gained from my time here.
I'd like to make the most of it in the future.
I would like to make use of them in the future. We would like to make the best use of it in the future and
We will also continue to work hard on our separate paths.
Thank you for your continued support.
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
Please continue.
Hallo! Ste.
Next, I would like to ask Ise-san some questions.
I'll do my best.
Next week on the 23rd, it will be your 5th anniversary.
What has had the biggest impact on you in the past 5 years?
It's difficult to choose the best one.
Recently, it was the concert at Yokohama Arena.
Ise-san loves to eat and walk around.
What kind of food have you been into recently?
Recently, it's my favorite
Gingko nuts!
It's been about half a year since a new member joined the group.
In a word, how would you describe your role in Angulum?
A grandmother who listens to you.
What do you like about Rocco?
What is your favorite thing about Rocco?
There are many things I like about Rocco.
She's so cute.
He's usually like a puppy.
But he's getting more and more mature.
She's studying herself.
I'm really enjoying your live performances.
It's like this sound... I don't know, it's like this sound.
This original feeling.
The way the song is sung.
I like that you can see the serious part of your research.
I like that I can see the seriousness of your research.
I also like the seriousness of your blog.
I also like the way she says she loves me.
But I also like the way you say you love me, and the way you say you love me.
Thank you very much!
Of all the Hello! Project singles of all time
Project singles of all time, which one has the most attractive jacket?
Angeleum's "Human Life," which should be loved.
Thank you very much!
I have a lot of questions for you.
If I had to sum up your role in Angulum in one word, it would be...
I'm not really a grandmother, but I'm a grandmother who really listens.
I'm not really a grandmother, but I'm a grandmother who listens.
I'm not the type of person who is usually too active in teaching.
I'm not very good at teaching.
It's not easy for me to do that.
But recently, for example, a new member, Hana Goto, came to me.
For example, a new member, Hana Goto, has been visiting us a lot.
She comes to me to talk about what's bothering her.
She comes to me to tell me what's bothering her, or to express how frustrated she is
She comes to me to tell me what's bothering her and how frustrated she is.
I can listen to her and tell her what's going on.
I can listen to what they have to say.
Give them a little bit of your time.
I'll be able to answer the questions so that everyone can be at ease. I wish I could be in such a position to answer the questions so that everyone can be at ease now.
I wish I could be in such a position
I'm playing the role of a grandmother.
I'm a big sister.
Another thing is that you let me say a lot of things I like about you.
Thank you very much.
Of course.
But really, Rocco...
But Rocco, even though you're all fluffy.
But you're so serious.
I really like your seriousness.
I hope you keep going straight ahead like Rocco.
I hope that you will continue to go straight ahead like Rocco.
I really want you to keep going straight like that.
That heart.
Thank you very much. We'll continue after this.
Japan 3! LDP! Japan Three!
Japan 3! LDP! Japan 3!
November 6, 2023
I, Yumeno Kishimoto, hereby announce that
Tsubaki Factory and Hello! Project.
After 11 years with Hello! Project for the past 11 years.
I've been supported by so many people
I've received so much love from so many people.
I have been able to come this far.
Thank you so much!
The story of Toriko Tsubaki Factory and I, Yumeno Kishimoto
will continue from now on, and I will continue to sing a lot of songs
I want to sing many songs and live on.
I hope to meet you again in the future. In the midst of it all, I hope to see you again.
I would like to express my love and gratitude to all the people I have met
I'll sing it in my own way, so please accept it.
I sing to you.
Good night
Good night, good night
Another day has dawned
I'm waiting for you. She's waiting for you.
It's a new morning
It's time for the first bell to ring.
No matter how late it is, you know it's waiting for you.
If you open the window and ask the sky...
I wonder if she'll know the answer.
I wonder if she knows...
Do you think she knows... that someday you will...
When you get to where she is
When you'll have all the answers
When you know all the answers
by H.
Today's fun
In the moment that counts
The best!
Words that were boring
I'm not counting.
I'll tell you what's next.
It's cool, right?
Look out!
Walk fast. I walk fast.
All over town.
We're rivals.
But we're all in this together
See, the guys who can get out of a pinch the best win.
And the lucky ones, they're the ones that land the lucky punches.
You see?
See, there's a dream in the world, and they're the ones who'll get the future.
A little betrayal.
me
Today I, Riko Yamagishi, am graduating from Tsubaki Factory and Hello Project.
First of all, I'd like to start by saying that dancing was the only thing I loved since I was a little girl, and I always wanted to be the best at recitals and events.
But other than that, I've always tried to hide behind others and keep a low profile in my life.
I applied for the trainee program not because I wanted to be an idol, but because I wanted to be a back-up dancer at Hello Project concerts.
I applied for the trainee program because I wanted to be a back-up dancer at Hello Project concerts rather than an idol, but they chose me as a trainee and a member of Hello Project.
I can't thank you enough for choosing me as a trainee and allowing me to work as a member of Tsubaki Factory until today.
Through my activities, I realized how cool and sparkling idols are.
Hello Project has made me realize how cool and sparkling idols are.
I am probably the least suited to be a leader among the group members.
I became the leader of the group and was almost crushed by the pressure every day.
When I looked at old videos, I thought I was doing the best I could at the time, but I was still somewhat intimidated and confident.
But I felt I was doing my best at that time, but I was looking somewhat frightened and unsure of myself.
I would like to thank all the members who have followed and supported such an unreliable leader.
I am filled with gratitude.
And the person who has supported me the most up to now is
I would like to express my gratitude to all the members who have supported me so far.
Whether it was cold in the middle of winter or scorching hot
with their light green goods and penlights
with light green goods and penlights. Here are all the fans who came from far and wide!
I am so happy to have met you all!
Thank you very much.
I love the members of Tsubaki Factory so much.
I'm a little bit sad that I won't be able to be with them from tomorrow.
I'll be watching over you all for a long time.
You'll be the leader tomorrow, but don't forget to be yourself.
If you're handy with the basics, you'll be fine.
I will miss Ami's laughter and loud sneezes.
You were always so calm and kind.
You were there for me through my graduation from Yumeko and that was really reassuring.
I respected Yume for having something that I didn't have.
Mizuho is friendly and sweet at times.
But she also had a firmness about her that helped me a lot.
I loved the way Saori looked so cute but was a little bit manly.
I hope she continues to be like that.
Maopin, I've never seen such a kind and loving girl.
Her positive cheerful attitude always saved my life.
Yumi is so caring and a big sister.
Yumi's energy always made me laugh.
Shiori's always straight and hardworking
I thought it was amazing.
Please let me have grilled rice again next time!
Marin is the perfect girl for the name of the Tsubaki group.
I love her core strength.
Luno may be the youngest, but he's more mature than everyone thinks.
Please keep up your honesty from now on.
I will treasure my work with Tsubaki Factory for the rest of my life.
Thank you for supporting Riko Yamagishi of Tsubaki Factory until now. Thank you for supporting Riko Yamagishi of Tsubaki Factory until now.
Thank you very much.
November 6, 2023 Riko Yamagishi, leader of Tsubaki Factory
Thank you for all your love.
Keep smiling every day.
With Isereira of Angelmi
Halo by Tsutsui Rocco of Ochanomama! Sta.
It's time to say goodbye.
We've brought you all the way to here.
How was it?
I don't know... I've been in quite a few places
About me...
I wish there was something I could say.
You've talked about me.
It's not often that we're alone together.
I've been able to talk to him a lot in the company of Rocco.
I was able to talk with Rocco a lot more.
I thought she's cute and I like her a lot.
And this serious part of Rocco that I said I liked...
I was very happy to see Rocco's serious side
I'm very happy to see the serious side of Rocco that I said I liked.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
I'm really happy.
I'm so happy to know that we're going to be able to shoot together.
I was told that we would be able to shoot together.
I was informed that we would be able to take pictures together about three months ago.
I was informed about 3 months ago that we would be able to take a picture together.
I was really looking forward to this day.
I was really looking forward to this day. Really looking forward to this day.
I've been working really hard every day
I'm really glad that I've been able to do this.
I never thought I'd be able to talk to you so close.
And I'm so happy that it's still on video.
I'm really, really happy
I'd like to see it a lot.
Thank you very much.
Here's an announcement!
Angulum Concert Tour 2023 Autumn
The 11 Angstroms are now underway!
The remaining shows are on Sunday, November 19th
Nippon Budokan on Sunday, November 19th and
and Friday, November 24th at Nippon Budokan.
One of the shows will be at Nippon Budokan.
I hope everyone will do their best until the end of both performances.
I hope we will all do our best until the end of the tour.
Yes, and Ocha no Oma Live Tour 2023!
Our hometown is in the middle of the Japan tour!
Saturday, November 25th in Fukuoka and Sunday, November 26th in Oita
and Sunday, November 26th in Oita prefecture.
We are still in the early stages of the tour, so we will continue to work together.
We will continue to work together to make it happen.
And Sunday, November 19th
Bizen City, Okayama Prefecture x Ocha-no-Oma Community Revitalization Concert
NARUCHIKA 2023 Ocha-no-Oma in Bizen
Okayama Prefecture is also Miki Nishizaki's hometown, so
I hope we can all get excited together in her hometown!
Yes, and on December 13th, Angulum's new single Yes, and on December 13th, Angulum's new single
Red Line Life is Beautiful will be released!
As I mentioned earlier, these two songs are really different from each other.
As I mentioned earlier, they are really two different songs.
This is the first single after the two new members joined the band.
I hope they will reach a lot of people.
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members
Hello Project members will appear on the channel more and more!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday.
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time I'll be talking with Reina Ise of Angulum and
and Ocha-no-mano-tsuiroko!
Good bye!
La La La La...
Last year's photogaphy... we laughed about how young we were...
The two of us are adults... but it's so sad...
The matching outfits, the matching pieces, the matching memories...
I've come a long way, that's a testament
The energy of this tailor-made future is too big.
Are you ready?
Don't overthink it.
Don't be no way
My life, it doesn't matter where it ends
Think of love and make it come true
Go ahead, you'll be fine
Just a little hesitation, let's do it
Still wait for sometime, for hesitation
Courage to live life to the fullest
LaLaLaLa... LaLaLaLa...
That formation that danced a dream more than a dream
Cloudy skies, I invited weakness.
LifeValva's only instagram is my past self.
I can be anything I want to be tomorrow.
The latest is the strongest.
I'm afraid of being alright again if it's full sail for 10 minutes.
I've got Tokyo, where I can get hurt a little, so I'll be alright, I won't give up
I don't feel like melting
Still, one day you'll have to wait
For the tears
I'll be alright
I'll choose my crush
And I'll see you again
I'll see you again in the future
La La La La La La...
La La La La La...
My life, it doesn't matter what the end point is
Each of us has love in our hearts, and we're going to make it come true
It's okay, there's no hesitation
Come on!
Let's do it!
I'll still be waiting for you someday
You're working it's my life
It's my life
Thank you very much.
It was a toucan prix.
Congratulations.
Good luck. Good luck.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Keyboard!
Thanks for your hard work.
Love it.
The name of the dream.
You can know.
Congratulations.
Let's all give a big hug.
You said we're all going to hug you.
That's not it. I'll say it.
I love you, Ricoa Yume.
I love you.
Thank you.
Good work.
Thank you for your hard work.
I, Riko Yamagishi, have graduated from Tsubaki Factory and Hello! Project.
When I put on the dress, I really felt that I was graduating,
The setlist for this Budokan concert was very special,
There were songs that looked back on the history of ℃-ute and songs by trainees,
I also had the opportunity to perform some songs by ℃-ute,
I think it was a very special set list,
During the songs, I would watch old videos in the back of the stage,
I think that the audience could enjoy comparing the old and the new images.
It was a live performance that made me feel the history of the show,
It was a live concert that made me feel a sense of history. I think it was a great live show.
It was a lot of fun.
We at Yamagishi will continue to do our best in a different way from Tsubaki,
I would like to do my best in a different way from Tsubaki,
I would like to ask for your continued support.
And about Tsubaki,
I'm looking forward to working with you,
I look forward to working with you.
This is Riko Yamagishi. Thank you very much.
I, Yumeno Kishimoto, graduated from Tsubaki Factory and Hello Project with the graduation performance on November 6.
I really feel that I have received a lot of love from you today,
We have received so much love through our daily activities as Tsubaki Factory, such as live performances, events, and responses on SNS,
I have received so much love from the members and from the team members who work together to make Tsubaki Factory,
I am glad to be a part of a group that is overflowing with love, and I am very happy to be there. Thank you very much.
I have been returning the love through my daily activities,
I think I have received more love from you than I can ever repay,
I believe that from now on, MATSUBAKI FACTORY will continue to move forward,
I would like to keep moving forward as a singer as well,
I would like to return the love through my activities,
Please keep your eyes on Riko, myself, and Tsubaki Factory.
Thank you very much.
This is Mino Kishimoto.